# DOAN QUOC BAO

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN**

baodq.dev@gmail.com \leftrightarrow linkedin.com/in/lluvh/ \leftrightarrow (+84) 343415138

#### **SUMMARY**

As a third year student with a passion for technology and web programming. I want to gain experience, build relationships during my internship to become a good engineer. Therefore, I hope I can apply my knowledge of web programming (Javascript, Restful API, SQL...) to complete the work well and contribute value to the company.

## **EDUCATION**

Major: Information Technology - University of Information Technology

Oct 2020 - Present

C/GPA: 8.32/10

Undergraduate Coursework: Computer networking, Operating Systems, Databases, Data structures and algorithms, Programming Languages and Technologies...

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Knowledge of programming languages like: Javascript, Typescript, C#(.NET).
- Experience with ReactJS, ExpressJS (Node.js), ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, Entity Framework.
- Have good knowledge about database (MongoDB, SQL Server).
- Knowledge of RESTful API.
- Have a good knowledge sense UX/UI Design.
- Understanding of Object Oriented Programming (OOP) and Algorithm.
- Have skill in using suitable tools include: Git, Jira, Figma...

## PROJECT EXPERIENCE

## **EARTH ENGLISH CENTER - WEBSITE**

Feb 2023 - May 2023

**Description:** CMS website that monitors the quality of students learning at an English center to predict output scores and give appropriate advice.

**Link FE:** https://github.com/nguyencongtanphat/englishCenterManagementFE.

**Link BE:** https://github.com/nksot21/IE213-English-Center-Quality-Management.

Technologies: ReactJS, NodeJS, MongoDB, Bootstrap, Firebase.

**Responsibilities:** Developer FE, BE and handle logic, Authorization, Design Database, Optimize designs to increaseproduct performance.

#### SHOWROOM CAR - WEBSITE

Step 2022 - Dec 2022

**Description:** A car showroom management website that includes managing cars, customers, employees and managing sales of the showroom.

**Link FE:** https://github.com/dangbalinh/showroomcar104.

**Link BE:** https://github.com/trung0302/ShowroomCarlS220.

Technologies: ReactJS, SQL Server, ASP. NET Core Web API, Entity Framework.

**Responsibilities:** Design UI and make UX decisions, Design Database, Write API and handle Backend for website, Authorization for API (JWT), Coding FE with ReactJS.

#### **HONORS & AWARDS**

**Excellent Student Scholarships 2020-2023:** Achieved good student scholarships for 5 consecutive semesters in the first 3 years.

**EVN Group Scholarship 2023:** Based on learning and training criteria, actively participating in social activities.

#### SOFT SKILLS

- Good Teamwork, Ability to think logically, Problem solving.
- Time managament, self-Study, research.
- Basic English communication, document reading and writings.